A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.14-RG 1.15 (A88-A89) FA478
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-1991; 1982-1988; 1.15; 44.84 Cubic Feet 37 standard record storage boxes (R2412-R2448) and 1 letter size document storage box (R2438A); Standard record storage boxes - Box R2412-Box R2448.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - University of Maryland - Shakespeare Teachers Institute (AH 8516), 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 137-139, Box 26, Folder 140-142)
      Folders 140-142 - Supplementary Material
    - Newberry Library - Humanities Conference (AH 8518), 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 143)
    - American Public Radio - Contemporary Music (AH 8520), 1983-1992 (Box 26, Folder 144, Box 27, Folder 145)
    - Arts International, Inc. (AH 8523), 1984-1992 (Box 27, Folder 146-148)
    - PEN American Center - International Congress (AH 8525), 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - Symphony Space - Radio Broadcasts of Literary Programs (AH 8529), 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 150)
    - New England Association of Schools & Colleges - Conference (AH 8530), 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 151-152)
      Folder 152 - Supplementary Material
    - Long Bow Group - China Film (AH 8533), 1984-1995 (Box 28, Folder 153)
    - 55th Street Dance Theater Foundation, Inc. - International Touring Network (AH 8536), 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 154)
    - Children's Books Feasibility Study (AH 8539), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 155-159)
      Folder 159 - Supplementary Material
    - Five Colleges, Inc. - Humanities Network (AH 8540), 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 160)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Visiting Scholar Data Base (AH 8549), 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 161)
    - Repertory Dance Theatre (of Utah) - 20th Anniversary Performances (AH 8602), 1985-1988 (Box 30, Folder 162)
    - Group I Acting Company, Inc. - "ORCHARDS: Seven American Playwrights Present Stories by Chekhov" (AH 8603), 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 163-164)
    - New York City Opera - Fire Emergency Fund for Sets and Costumes (AH 8605), 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 165-166)
    - Readers International - Contemporary Non-Western Literature (AH 8611), 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 167-168)
      Folder 168 - Supplementary Material
    - Downtown Community Television Center, Inc. - Building (AH 8617), 1986-1990 (Box 31, Folder 169-170)
    - Center for Understanding Media, Inc. - Picture Opera (AH 8618), 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 171-172)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers-Civic Responsibility Conference (AH 8631), 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 173-174)
    - Minnesota Composers Forum - American Music (AH 8637), 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 175)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - University of Georgia - Wildlife Management in Suriname (AS 8506), 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 176)
    - International Society for Plant Molecular Biology - International Congress (AS 8508), 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 177)
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases - Hans Jahnke (AS 8509), 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 178)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center - Denitrification Losses (AH 8512), 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 179)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center - Wide Cross Program on Wheat (AS 8514), 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 180)
    - International Trypanotolerance Centre - Consultant (AS 8518), 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 181)
    - International Service for National Agricultural Research - Consultants (AS 8519), 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 182)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Achola Okeyo (AS 8520), 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 183)
    - Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agriculture (AS 8525), 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 184-185)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Tissue Culture Laboratory Equipment (AS 8526), 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 186)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management - Fund Raising Program (AS 8529), 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 187-188)
    - Fudan University - Institute of Genetics (AS 8531), 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 189)
    - Max-Planck-Institute for Plant Breeding - Electrotransformation (AS 8533), 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 190)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - W. Thomas Conelly (AS 8534), 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 191)
    - University of Florida - Gender Issues in Farming Systems (AS 8540), 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 192)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Publication, Rice Genetics (AS 8541), 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 193)
    - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization - Tissue Culture (AS 8542), 1983-1987 (Box 35, Folder 194, Box 36, Folder 195)
    - University of California (Davis) - Salt Tolerance in Cereals (AS 8601), 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 196)
    - Biotechnology of Cereal Crops - Workshop (AS 8602), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 197)
    - World Resources Institute - World Bank and International Agricultural Development (AS 8605), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 198)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Symposium on Chromosome Engineering in Plants (AS 8613), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 199)
    - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Review (AS 8617), 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 200)
    - International Rice Research Institute - Workshop on Biotechnology for Crop Improvement (AS 8623), 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 201)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management - Tilapia Breeding (AS 8631), 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 202-203)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - Baylor College of Medicine - Conference on High School Math and Science Improvement Programs (EO 8502), 1984-1986 (Box 37, Folder 204)
    - City College of New York - Bridge to Graduate Study in Science Program (EO 8504), 1982-1987 (Box 37, Folder 205-207)
    - Exploratorium - Explainer Program (EO 8509), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 208)
    - Tulane University - Conference on Voting Rights and the Democratic Process (EO 8510), 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 209-210)
      Folder 210 - Supplementary Material
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #1B, 2017:FA478:003 (Box 38, Folder 210)
        Video cassette tape
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #2B, 2017:FA478:004 (Box 38, Folder 210)
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #3B, 2017:FA478:005 (Box 38, Folder 210)
      - Voting Rights Conference: "Voting Rights and the Democratic Process", March 29, 1985, Center for Legal Studies on Intergovernmental Relations, Tulane University, Tape #4B, 2017:FA478:006 (Box 38, Folder 210)
    - Inuit Circumpolar Conference - Alaska Native Review Commission, Study of Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act (EO 8512), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 211-214)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education, Inc. - Citizen Empowerment Project (EO 8514)), 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 215)
    - University of Michigan - National Black Election Study (EO 8515), 1983-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 216-221, Box 40, Folder 222-224)
      Folders 221-224 - Supplementary Material
    - Ellen Lewin - Gender Role Grant (EO 8518), 1985-1987, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 225-226)
    - National Senior Citizens Law Center - Women and Pensions (EO 8519), 1985-1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 227)
    - University of Michigan - Dual-Family Child Support (EO 8522), 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 228)
    - Southern Education Foundation - Continuing Conference in Public Policy and Education (EO 8524), 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 229-233)
      Folder 233 - Supplementary Material
    - New York Urban League - Membership Campaign (EO 8525), 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 234)
    - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation, Inc. - Conference on the Economic Status of Black Women (EO 8529), 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 235)
    - Joint Center for Political Studies, Inc. - Conference of Black Scholars (EO 8530), 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 236)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. - Special Committee of the Board (EO 8531), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 237-238)
    - University of Illinois - Sex Composition of Occupations, 1970-1980 (EO 8533), 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 239, Box 43, Folder 240)
    - Urban Institute - Child Care and Self-Sufficiency for Welfare Mothers Project (EO 8537), 1981-1991 (Box 43, Folder 241-245)
    - Institute for Puerto Rican Policy, Inc. - Hispanic Voter Registration Trends in New York City (EO 8538), 1985-1989 (Box 44, Folder 246-247)
    - Cornell University - National Conference on Economic Dislocation and Job Loss (EO 8541), 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 248)
    - Carol B. Stack - Culture of Gender Among Women and Men of Color (EO 8542), 1985-1989 (Box 44, Folder 249)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Youth and Labor Market (EO 8607), 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 250, Box 45, Folder 251)
    - Piton Foundation - Concept Paper, Denver Underclass (EO 8627), 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 252)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - Queensland Institute of Medical Research - Diagnosis and Prevention of Flavivirus Infections (HS 8503), 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 253)
    - Ferrucio Santoro - Study to Develop Vaccine Against Leishmaniasis (HS 8506), 1982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 254)
    - University of Victoria - Molecular Studies on African Trypanosomes (HS 8513), 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 255-256)
    - Mahidol University - Studies of Infection and Morbidity of Helminth Parasites (HS 8516), 1982-1986 (Box 46, Folder 257-258)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Conference on Medical Education and the Humanities (HS 8523), 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 259)
    - HS 8527 Oxford University - Thalassemia in Pacific Islanders, 1985-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8528 Harvard University - Psychiatry, 1982-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8532 Chen Pei-Yuan, 1985-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8533 Princeton University - Control programs, 1982-1986 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8535 International Epidemiology Assn. - Brazil conf., 1984-1987 (Box R2430)
    - HS 8601 University Hospitals, Cleveland - Onchocera Volvulus, 1984-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8602 Egwang, Thomas, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8603 Freeman, Phyllis K., 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8605 University of Connecticut - Schistosomiasis, 1984-1989 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8606 London School of Hygiene - Leprosy, 1984-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8609 World Fed. for Medical Ed. - Conferences, 1985-1988 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8620 United Nations - World Health Org. - Assembly, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8536 International Federation of Scientific Editors' Associations - Nairobi Symposium, 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8541 Blair Research Laboratory - Praziquantel, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8543 New York University - Malaria Studies In Africa, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8548 Mata, Leonardo 85-87, 19[?] (Box R2431)
    - HS 8549 University of Pennsylvania - Stipend and Health Insurance, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8851 Rosero Bixby, Luis 85-89 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8552 London School Of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Leishmania, 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8554 United Nations - World Health Organization - Regional Office for Africa, 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8555 University of California - Parasitic Invasion Symposium (L.A.), 1985-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8556 Johnson, Rollin B., 1983-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8630 Ntambi, James M., 1985-1986 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8632 U.S. & Thai Officials - Consultative Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box R2431)
    - HS 8644 Emory University - Carter Center - Global Consult. on Health Conference, 1986-1986 (Box R2431)
  - International Relations (IR)
    - IR 8501 French Institute of International Relations - Lebanon Conference, 1984-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8509 Aspen Institute - Governance in a World Economy, 1982-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8512 U.N. Association - U.S. Economic Policy, 1985-1987 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8520 Columbia University - Phadnis, 1985-1986 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8522 Global Interdependence Center - Monetary Conference, 1982-1986 (Box R2432)
    - IR 8523 Southern Africa - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2433)
      Scope and Contents note
      One Supplementary Folder - additional folder in [unreadable].
    - IR 8525 International Economics Association - Conference, 1984-198[?] (Box R2433)
    - IR 8526 Western Australian Institute of Technology - Publication, 1985-198[?] (Box R2433)
    - IR 8527 Wilson International Center for Scholars - W. European Program, 1985-1986 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8530 University of Pittsburgh - Atlantic Alliance and Middle East, 1984-1988 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8532 American Assembly - Easing East - West Tensions in the Third World, 1985-1987 (Box R2433)
    - IR 8530 University of Pittsburgh - Atlantic Alliance and Middle East, 1984-1988 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8532 American Assembly - Easing E-W - Tensions in the Third World, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8533 Laba, Roman, 1983-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8534 Center for a New Democracy - Pacific Rim Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8536 Overseas Development Council - World Bank Future, 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8537 World Peace Foundation - Inter - American Collective Security, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8538 Georgetown University - African Debt & Financing Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8541 Potter, William C., 1985-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8601 Journal of Interdisciplinary History - Origins and Prevention of War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8604 African Association of Political Science - S. African Conference, 1986-1986 (Box R2434)
    - IR 8605 International Human Rights Law Group - Liberian Trials, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8606 Bekich, Darko, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8607 Institute for International Economics - Agriculture and the GATT, 1986-1989 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8608 Emory University - Carter Center - Debt Crisis Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8612 Geneva Graduate Institute of International Studies - Iran-Iraq War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8615 New York Academy of Sciences - Technology & Risk of War Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8622 Fundacin Mediterrnea - Economics Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8623 Reiss, Mitchell B., 1985-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8624 Chinese Scholars of International Studies - Conference, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8625 Church of the Pilgrims - Network for Human Rights in Liberia, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
    - IR 8631 Institute for International Economics - Conference, 1986-1987 (Box R2435)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 8504 International Union for Scientific Study of Population - Italy Conference, 1984-1987 (Box R2435)
    - PS 8507 University of Connecticut - Guinea pig sperm antigen, 1984-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8509 Population Council, Inc. - Immunology Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8510 University of Massachusetts - Progesterone, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8511 National Academy of Sciences - Population Growth, 1983-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8512 International Women's Health Coalition - Contraceptive Failure Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8513 University of Bahia - Mascarenhas, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8517 Colegio de Mxico - Latin American Population Program, 1985-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8520 Cornell University - Sperm antibody Formation, 1983-1986 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8521 Leshabari, M.T., 1984-1985 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8526 American Assembly - Population Policy, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8527 Rosero-Bixby, L.A., 1985-1988 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8528 Catholic University (Chile) - Human Reproductive Conference, 1985-1988 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8531 Rockefeller University - Reproduction and Catechol Estrogens, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8532 Rockefeller University - Progestin action in Reproduction, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8601 Institute of Biology - Pituitary and Estrogen Receptors, 1985-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8602 Marine Biological Laboratory (Woods Hole) - Video Microscopy Training, 1986-1987 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8611 Aghajanian, A. 86-87 (Box R2436)
    - PS 8613 McMaster University - Indian Scientists Travel, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8504 University of Nairobi - Women's issues, 1984-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8505 Magubane, Peter, 1984-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8508 Council on Foundations, Inc. - Business leaders Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8511 Obor, Inc. - Solidarity issue, 1983-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8512 National Museums of Kenya - Paleoanthropology school, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8513 International Bank - RF & Indian Agricultural Development, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8514 University of Georgia Law School Association - Rusk Papers, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8516 Williams College - Development Politics and Economics Training Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8517 Andrews, Penelope E., 1984-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8520 Women In Need, Inc. - Child Care, 1985-1988 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8523 New York University - Portfolio Management, 1984-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8525 Partnership for Productivity International - African Food Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8529 Indiana University - African Art and Museums Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8530 Women's Funding Coalition - DAWN Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2437)
    - SIE 8531 United Nations Office for Emergency Operations in Africa, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8532 Kohler, Robert E., 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8533 National Council for Research on Women - Women's Dialogue (US/USSR), 1984-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8535 Okin, Susan M., 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8537 University of California - Gender & Mobility in America (L.A. ), 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8538 Harvard University - Women's Contribution to Family Economy, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8539 Norton, Mary Beth, 1985-1986 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8540 Cornell University - Children's Thinking About Gender, 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8602 Social Science Research Council - Foreign Language International Studies, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8606 Aga Khan Foundation U.S.A. - Sub-Saharan Africa Conference, 1985-1987 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8607 CILECT - Training in Developing Countries, 1985-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8608 Salzburg Seminar - Philanthropy & Non-Profit Institution, 1986-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8609 Gender, Technology & Development - Workshop, 1986-1988 (Box R2438)
    - SIE 8611 Independent Sector - Forum & Guidebook on Community Services, 1986-1987 (Box R2438)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - Brambila Paz, Carlos, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - Chillik, Claudio Fabian, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - Rios Nete, Edward Luiz Gonalves, 1985-1987 (Box R2439)
    - Vilar - Rojas, Cecilia, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A40 Sichuan Medical College - Clinical epidemiology, 1985-198[?] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A42 Third Annual Meeting of INCLEN, 1984-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A45 Addis Ababa University - Clinical epidemiology, 1985-198[?] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A47 Shanghai Medical University - Hua Shan Hospital, 1985-19[unreadable] (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A48 Khon Kaen University - Clinical epidemiology - Kiertyia & Sumir, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A49 Chulalongkorn University - Clinical epidemiology - Ayut D., 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A50 West China University of Medical Science - Clinical epidemiology - Lei Bingjun, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A51 Paulista Medical School - Clinical epidemiology - Atallah, Sesso, & Goihman, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A52 Mahidol University - Clinical epidemiology - Nalinee and Nirun, 1985-1989 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85004 - A55 Fourth Annual Meeting of INCLEN, 1985-1986 (Box R2439)
    - RF 85011 - A36 Harvard University - Gossypol, 1982-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A380 Murird, Lion, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A381 Gilbert, Martin, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A382 Bair, Deirdre, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A383 Swearer, Donald K., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A84 Brandt, Allan M., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A385 Gibbard, Allan F., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A386 Kemper, Steven E.G., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A387 Mc Murry, Linda O., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A388 Mack, Phyllis, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A389 Miller, Nancy K., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A390 Offen, Karen, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A391 Thompson, Margaret Susan, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A392 Walkowitz, Judith R., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A393 Kessner, Thomas, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A394 Tick, Judith, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A395 Harris, Michael Wesley, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A396 Johnson, Penelope D., 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A397 Herbert, Robert L., 1984-1988 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A398 Keller, Evelyn Fox, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85013 - A399 Marcus, Judith, 1984-1987 (Box R2440)
    - RF 85014 - A2 Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe - Interdisciplinary artists, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85018 West Africa Rice Development Association - Staff Support, 1983-1989 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85025 National Humanities Center - Fellowships for Junior Scholars, 1984-1991 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A107 Landry, L. Bartholemew, 1985-1989 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A108 Edwards, Lillie Johnson, 1985-1986 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A109 Thomas, Gail E., 1985-1988 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A110 Perry, Huey L., 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A111 Nelson - Legall, Sharon, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A112 Paterson - Lewis, Sonja, 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85032 - A113 Davis, Thadius M., 1985-1987 (Box R2441)
    - RF 85034 Editorial Projects in Education - Education week, 1984-1985 1987 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85038 Learning in Focus - Films for Television, 1983-1987 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85040 National Arts Stabilization Fund, 1988-1989 (Box R2442)
    - RF 85040 National Arts Stabilization Fund, 1982-1987 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85042 - A3 Yu Yongxin, 1984-1986 1988 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85042 - A4 Mahidol University - Neurosafety primate testing, 1985-1988 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85045 International Planned Parenthood Federation - Developing World Program, 1986-1989 (Box R2443)
    - RF 85045 International Planned Parenthood Federation - Developing World Program, 1984-1985 (Box R2444)
    - RF 85052 Clark College - Public Policy Studies, 1973-1987 (Box R2444)
    - RF 85052 Clark College (Supplementary Folders), 1991 (Box R2445)
    - RF 85052 Clark College - Public Policy Studies (Supplementary folders), 1991 (Box R2446)
    - RF 85069 National Urban League - Permanent development fund, 1985-1989 (Box R2446)
    - RF 85078 - A115 Tufts University - Geographic medicine, 1977-1987 (Box R2446)
    - RF 85088 Urban Affairs Partnership - Philadelphia schools and humanities, 1983-1987 (Box R2447)
    - RF 86021 Guttmacher Institute - Adolescent pregnancy, 1978-1988 (Box R2448)